[{"question": " what is it hon?", "answer": " i-i can\u0092t find anything that i want to eat! everything i eat makes me nauseous! i\u0092m telling you, being pregnant is no piece of cake\u0097ooh! cake!  no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " aww, honey i\u0092m sorry.", "answer": " god! ooh! what is that smell? it\u0092s coming from the bathroom. ooh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " it\u0092s me. it\u0092s phoebe. listen there\u0092s something in here i want to eat, what-what smells so good?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " is it the shampoo? it\u0092s guava.", "answer": "  no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " oh! wait-wait!  is it my bologna sandwich?", "answer": " yes. yes. yes. i can\u0092t believe it! the baby wants bologna! maybe he wants me to eat meat? i can\u0092t eat meat!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " what are you writing?", "answer": " well, joshua\u0092s coming in tomorrow and since i don\u0092t have the guts to ask him out, i\u0092m going to sell him a coat and put this note in the pocket.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " hi guys!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hey, what have you guys been up too?", "answer": " oh, we went to see a collection of victorian doorknobs and the cupert-hewitt museum.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " without me?!", "answer": " my uncle dragged us there. but, it actually it turned out to be really interesting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " they were so ornate and beautiful, i mean look at that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know how museums work in england but, here, you\u0092re not supposed to take stuff.", "answer": " i uh, i got it from the gift shop. they have really lax security there.  it\u0092s a joke.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " wow! you guys seem to be having a good time.", "answer": " oh yeah, she\u0092s-she\u0092s amazing. and-and she\u0092s so much fun. and! y\u0092know what? when i\u0092m with her, i\u0092m fun! i even signed up for helicopter classes.  she\u0092s leaving in two days, i don\u0092t have to do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " oh no, two days, you must be bummed.", "answer": " yeah, she\u0092s got to go back to london. but you know what? i\u0092ve been prepared for this from the start. we both knew we had two weeks together, and that\u0092s it. y\u0092know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " hey that\u0092s what all my relationships are like.", "answer": " yes, but in ross\u0092s case, they both know in two weeks that\u0092s it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " pheebs!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": "  hello! hello!", "answer": "  yes! i know! i know! yeah! so the baby is totally craving meat. this afternoon i tried tricking it, i made it a soy-burger to make it think it was getting meat, y\u0092know? and i got nauseous.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " maybe that\u0092s because soy-burgers suck!", "answer": " being pregnant is tough on your tummy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " hey, but at least you got that cool, pregnant lady glow.", "answer": " that\u0092s sweat. you throw up all morning, you\u0092ll have that glow too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": "  okay!", "answer": " oh, here\u0092s that trench-coat that you wanted.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " oh great!  wow! yeah, it\u0092s comfortable.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": "  oh no-no, no-no, they don\u0092t want you to put your hands in the pockets until you are out of the store.", "answer": " why not?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " y\u0092know, they ruin it for everybody.", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " y\u0092know, i wore that cashmere sweater on a date last night.", "answer": " oh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " yeah, it was my first date since the uh, since the divorce.", "answer": " well, congratulations, so do you love her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " no, no, no, she\u0092s nice but, y\u0092know, it just it made me realize that i\u0092m just not, i\u0092m just not ready to be dating, y\u0092know?", "answer": " huh. well, uh, that\u0092s uh, that\u0092s interesting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  hey-whoa-hey-hey, what was that?", "answer": " oh, it\u0092s just an anti-theft device.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " oops, sorry. listen, we-we have to have a party tonight! actually, we have to have one in five minutes, so everybody cancel your plans.", "answer": " what are you talking about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " yeah, what\u0092 going on?", "answer": " we have to have a surprise bon voyage party for emily. but it\u0092s actually for joshua.  look, he said he\u0092s not ready to date, so i had to invite him to a party if i wanted to see him outside of work, and now i have the perfect opportunity to seduce him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " well, as much as i\u0092d like to meet josh and warn him, emily and i aren\u0092t going to be here. all right? i mean, she\u0092s going to come by first to say good-bye, and then i\u0092ve got a whole special evening planned. so i\u0092m sorry, no party.", "answer": " awwww!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": "  hello?", "answer": " surprise!!! chandler and joey: surprise!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " no one\u0092s ever thrown me a surprise party before!", "answer": " well, it was all ross\u0092s idea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " you\u0092re so sweet! and i\u0092m so surprised!", "answer": " you really didn\u0092t know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " uhh, because i\u0092m trying to play hard to get. oh, quick he\u0092s looking over here, say something funny.", "answer": " like what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " what-what-what is so funny?", "answer": " i said, \"like what?\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " now that\u0092s a thinker.", "answer": " okay, y\u0092know what, y\u0092know what? this playing hard to get thing is not working. umm, hand-hand me those cherries.  okay. okay.  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " care for a cherry?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " oh, no thanks.", "answer": " no? y\u0092know, i can tie one of these into a knot using just my tongue.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  so we should probably get going soon.", "answer": " oh, but the party\u0092s only just getting started!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " yeah, but we-we have to be at the four seasons for drinks in 15 minutes and then y\u0092know, then the plaza for dinner.", "answer": " so why did you plan a party at the same time?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " no-no-no, no, umm, actually american surprise parties are-are-are very short. it\u0092s usually, \"surprise!\" and then, \"oh my god, i\u0092m so surprised\u0097good-bye!\"", "answer": " but ross, i\u0092m such having a great time! your sister has just been telling me that you used to dress up like little, old ladies and hold make-believe tea parties.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " ooh, yeah. then what are you going to put on top of that?", "answer": " a little salami.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " ooh yeah! then umm, what goes on top of the salami?", "answer": " pastrami.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " oh, could somebody give me a hand with this zipper?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " up!", "answer": " you changed?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " yeah, i did. i needed my lucky dress.", "answer": " and lucky means, more cleavage?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " ohh, god! look at him, he\u0092s so cute. i wanna go over there, grab him, and kiss him! how can i kiss him and not letting him know that i like him?", "answer": " oh! i know how you can get him, take off your bra.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " there was a seen in footloose...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " flashdance.", "answer": " yeah-yeah, yeah, with that-that uh, plumber girl\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " she was a welder.", "answer": " what? were you like in the movie, or\u009a anyway, she takes off her bra under her shirt and pulls it out the sleeve. very sexy, and classy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " or if you want to kiss him, umm, you could use mistletoe.", "answer": " it\u0092s not christmas!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " or spin the bottle?", "answer": " he\u0092s not 11!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": "  thank you so much for this. it was really so thoughtful of you.", "answer": " what? you\u0092re leaving?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " yes, we have something we have to get to.", "answer": " uhh, yeah, i think i\u0092m going to take-off too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " no! you guys can\u0092t leave yet! you have to stay, we-we got the whole big thing planned!", "answer": " what big thing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": "  so, spin the bottle works like this: i spin the bottle, it lands on gunther, so i would have to kiss gunther.  all right. who wants to go first?", "answer": " i\u0092ll go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": "  okay, that-that\u0092s enough! y\u0092know, let\u0092s, let\u0092s let someone else play.", "answer": " if you didn\u0092t want to play, why did you come to the party?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " oh my god!! the baby just kicked!", "answer": " ohh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " it\u0092s okay! it\u0092s okay! it kicked once, it\u0092ll kick again!", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " y\u0092know it doesn\u0092t matter how much i\u0092m craving it. y\u0092know why i\u0092m never gonna eat meat? because it\u0092s murder, cold blooded murder.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " phoebe, what-what are you doing?!", "answer": " i can\u0092t help it. i need the meat. the baby needs the meat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " all right look, y\u0092know how-y\u0092know how when you\u0092re dating someone and you don\u0092t want to cheat on them, unless it\u0092s with someone really hot?", "answer": " yeah, totally!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " feel better now?", "answer": " yeah, but at what cost? six more months, three meals a day, i\u0092m gonna eat like, y\u0092know millions of cows.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " hey, what if i said, i could even things out for ya, meatwise.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " well, i eat a lot of meat right?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " well, suppose until the baby\u0092s born i laid off it. no extra animals would die, you-you\u0092d just be eating my animals.", "answer": " joey, i can\u0092t believe you would do that for me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " but, we can\u0092t go now. it looks like rachel\u0092s gonna put on a skit.", "answer": " oh my god! have you lost your mind?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " no-n-n-n-no! i am finally thinking clearly. my lucky dress wasn\u0092t working out to well for me, but for four years, this baby never missed.", "answer": " rachel-rachel-rachel i-i cannot, i can\u0092t let\u0097, actually i kinda want to see what happens.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " nice uh, costume.", "answer": " ohh, yeah, well i wanted to give emily a big american good-bye cheer. so okay!  ready! okay! gimme an \u0091e!\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " e!", "answer": " gimme an \u0091m!\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " m!", "answer": " gimme an \u0091i!\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " i!", "answer": " gimme an \u0091l!\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " l!", "answer": " gimme a \u0091y!\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " y!", "answer": " what do you get?  emily!!  emil\u0097whoa!!  okay! so that\u0092s me as a cheerleader! ta-dum!   joey and monica: are you all right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " i\u0092m fine! i\u0092m fine! i\u0092m just losing a tooth, it\u0092s no big deal. i have a dentist! y\u0092know. i\u0092m gonna go put some ice on it. excuse me.  what do i do now? what do i do now?", "answer": " i think you\u0092re done.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " umm, that was really great, but i-i gotta take-off actually.", "answer": "  take the bra off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " all right, come on, let\u0092s go get your coat.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " so, this was uh, really fun.", "answer": " oh, yeah! real fun.  y\u0092know, this bra\u009a really, bothers me.  y\u0092know, this used to be my bedroom. yeah. a lot of memories in here, a lot of memories. if these walls could talk, y\u0092know what they\u0092d say? wanna hear some memories?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " need uh, need a little hand there.", "answer": " oh no-no-no! no, i got this all under control.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " ughhhh!! forget it!  this is, this is not how this is supposed to happen.", "answer": " well, what was supposed to happen?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " can you not look at me when i say this?  i thought that if i could get you here, i could seduce you.", "answer": " huh. oh, boy!  uhh, i-i don\u0092t wear suits to work, and i bought six of them from you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " well, i\u0092m sorry, i thought you needed them!", "answer": " no, no-no, no-no, my point is that i kept coming back because, i wanted to see you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " why?!", "answer": " because i-i like you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " you like me?", "answer": " yeah! i mean you\u0092re-you\u0092re beautiful and smart and sophisticated\u0097a lot of this isn\u0092t based on tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " yeah but-but-but you liked me! oh my god, i can\u0092t believe this, all this time, i liked you and you liked me!", "answer": " but\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " oh no-no-no don\u0092t say but! no-no, but\u0092s never good! let\u0092s just leave it at, you like me and i like you.", "answer": " okay uh, however\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " oh, now see that\u0092s a fancy but.", "answer": " my marriage like just ended, and i\u0092m really not ready to get into anything yet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " but\u009a.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, i, i just need a little time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " ohh, here you are. i was looking for you before. joshua\u0092s gone so you and emily are free to go.", "answer": " that\u0092s okay. she\u0092s still in there enjoying her fake party and uh, it\u0092s too late to do any of the things i had planned, so\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " oh, ross, i\u0092m sorry. i completely ruined your evening.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " well, if it makes you feel any better, i made a fool out of myself.", "answer": " helps a little.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " is there room on that step for a pathetic loser?", "answer": " yeah, have a seat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " i\u0092m so sorry.", "answer": " that\u0092s okay, i mean it was just two-week thing anyway, i just didn\u0092t want it to end this way, y\u0092know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " well, maybe you didn\u0092t want it to end?", "answer": " what do you mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " you seem to really like her.", "answer": " yeah, i really do. yeah, but what am i gonna do, i mean we-we both agreed that it was gonna be a two-week thing, y\u0092know no commitment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " ross, that girl just spent the entire evening talking to your friends, asking to hear stories about you, looking through monica\u0092s photo albums, i mean you don\u0092t do that if you\u0092re just in it for two weeks.", "answer": " you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " yeah, you got like 14 hours until she has to be at the airport, and you\u0092re sitting here in the hallway with a 28-year-old cheerleader with a fat lip.", "answer": " hey, you\u0092re right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " thanks.  what photo album was it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know, it was you and a bunch of albino kids.", "answer": " oh my god! those weren\u0092t albino kids, that was computer camp! rach!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " you\u0092re a pathetic loser, right?", "answer": " oh-ho, yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " oh my gosh, joshua!", "answer": " all those things i said about not being ready\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " they\u0092re not true?", "answer": " no, they\u0092re-they\u0092re all true.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " but\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " you wanna go inside and have some coffee?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " oooh, what you got there?", "answer": " pastrami.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " oh-ho-ho, yeah! hey! y\u0092know what goes good with that?", "answer": " hm-mm, corn beef.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " ooh, i was gonna say bologna, but that\u0092s much better. how about a little of that smoked turkey?", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": "  oh mama! uh when-when is the baby due?", "answer": " six months.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " ugh. now if a cow should die of natural causes, i can have one of those right?", "answer": " not if i get there first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}]